Oh god, somebody help me. I think I
falling again.
This ain't healthy, but I don't want no
other man.
91.
I need you, please.
Somebody help stop me before it gets too
late. Operator, come get me. 515. It's
an emergency.
>> Miss Spitfire, it is of my great
privilege to welcome you and your Wonder
Bulls to our small, quaint town of
Ponyville. I know you're so used to
flying, so I pray that you did not dirty
your hooves by stepping in any of our
horseshit. We did, unfortunately. My
ponies will get back to your ponies for
the hoof cleaning fee. Bleach,
water,
more bleach. Twilight Sparkle and her
band of lesbian horses have been ordered
by our great ruler, Princess Celestia at
gunpoint to perform a special musical
number to show our appreciation for the
joys and wonder you spread all around
Equestria. Now, mayor, is this your way
of trying to build good relations
between the Wonderbolts and your stinky
little town, you dirty [__] We have
been looking to build more flight tracks
in this area. So perhaps Ponyville could
do with some good old gentrification.
>> Building a flight track in the city
limits would demolish like 50 houses,
commander. But maybe we could build the
flight track right outside town. Sorry.
>> Gosh darn it, Fluttershy. Can't you do
anything right?
>> Sorry,
Br. I thought you were back home in
Appaloosa. The moment I realized I was
dropping a shipment of apples in
Ponyville on the same day you'd be
stopping by here on your Wonderbolt
tour, I wanted to surprise you. Hey,
Spitfire. Hey, fruit cup. Not that I'm
unhappy to see you, Brayburn, but I'm
working now. I've got a panel I've got
to get to with the Ponyville Town
Council.
>> It does sound mighty important. Even my
cousin Applejack is in on it, and she
told me nothing. I'll be sitting in the
middle row, so make sure to look at me.
Spitfire, since you're our guest, would
you like to start off by explaining the
reason that you're here? You bet your
fat ass I would, my good [__] Every
pony, after looking through Ponyville's
city records, the Wonderbolts have
uncovered something very interesting.
For years, Ponyville, under orders of
Princess Celestia, has been practicing
the age-old act of redlinining. Certain
neighborhoods and housing districts have
secretly been reserved just for unicorns
and Pegasus, while Earth ponies have
been pushed toward the outskirts.
>> Granny, is that why we poop in an
outhouse on the farm while the rest of
Ponyville's got plumbing?
>> These areas mostly unicorns. These
districts, mostly Pegasus, and the Earth
ponies out here. And now.
And now.
>> Brin, can you please put the apple away?
There's no eating during the panel.
>> I'm not eating an apple.
>> Hun, you don't have to lie. We all saw
you take a bite of the apple.
>> And now the Wonderbolts.
>> Brayburn. I thought that if I bit down
slower, you wouldn't hear my munching
and crunching. We still can.
>> I'm sorry. And now the Wonderbolts are
going to continue the good old tradition
of redlinining. Mama is going to
demolish Sweet Apple Acres and build a
brand new Wonderbolts flight track right
here in Ponyville. A massive facility
with training grounds, a stadium,
hotels, shops, and tourists coming in
from all across Equestria.
>> But Big Mac, Speed Up Lake is our home.
>> But most importantly, that means more
money for poopyville. The prices will go
up and Earth ponies may find that they
can no longer afford to live here at
all. But that's the price to pay for
progress. You hear that girls, us
Pegasus and unicorns are as good as
butter.
>> Twilight, ain't no pony. Tell me about
this.
>> Applejack, stop. I already signed off on
the demolition.
>> Girl, are you pooping on my butt?
>> Gal pal. Your family's farm is the
biggest plot of land in Ponyville, and
we already get enough apples outsourced
from your cousin Brain's farm. The 67
acres of land you got would be far
better put to use for other avenues. I
have already come to terms with the
reality that this may destroy our
friendship. And if me and the girls
become the main five instead of the main
six starting today, then so be it.
You see, Applejack, all you Earth ponies
know is violence. This is why you're
wrong and I'm right.
>> And what would a demolition project be
without its demolition manager? How
about we give a warm round of applause
for Octavia Pie? Oh my god, it's Pinkie
Pie's far more successful but not
well-known gay brother, Octavia Pie, who
appeared in the Friendship of Magic
spin-off series Pony Life for one
episode.
Damn it, Octavia. Why must you upstage
me at everything I've ever done my whole
entire life? How could you? You're an
Earth pony, too, and you're going to
displace us. This affects you, too.
>> Octavia Pie is not just an Earth pony
sister, dear. Octavia Pie is a traveling
earth pony. Let's get that straight at
least. And you know very much how little
things about Octavia Pie are straight.
WHY EXACTLY SHOULD Octavia care what
happens to your stupid little town?
Hell, why should Octavia care about
anything that happens to you after the
family threw Octavia out on the streets?
Father, Octavia sat on a rock last night
and it went up Octavia's butt and
Octavia liked it. So Octavia regrets to
inform you that Octavia Pie is gay.
>> That is a damn shame because being gay
has nothing to do with rocks. I suppose
it's time for you to go. Can Octavia say
goodbye to Octavia's sisters before
Octavia goes?
>> No.
>> But Daddy, we're going to miss Octavia.
>> Limestone, go to the tool shed outside
and grab the whip so this family can be
reminded what happens when a child
speaks back to their parent in the world
of My Little Pony.
>> Why do you refer to yourself in third
person? Rainbow Dash. Every pony, a part
of the pie lineage is inbred. It's best
not to dwell on the concept of logic.
>> Your limo ran over my baby, you psycho.
Sell that autograph on eBay, ma'am. Is
worth more than enough to replace a
baby.
>> Saurin, you're here. Care packages bail
today is 780,000.
Well, that's lower than last week at
least.
>> Yeah, he only unalived seven ponies this
week. I'm so proud of him.
>> What's with the uniform?
>> You know how it is, cousin Brayburn. The
family doesn't want me working on the
farm since I'm dating a criminal. So,
mama's got to do some door dashing to
put food on the table.
>> Apple bottom, I can't keep doing this
for you guys.
>> Why not? You're rich.
>> It's not about the price. If word gets
out that I'm using a significant portion
of the Wonderbolts funds to keep bailing
your boyfriend out of the psych ward,
it's not going to be a good look for me.
Mr. Care package, you've been bailed
out.
>> Don't you mean you missed these?
>> Apple bottom. Look, we did macaroni art
again today.
>> I'm trying to show you my flat tits. Use
20 noodles so that we can each have 10
for dinner. So that we don't have to go
to the food bank today.
>> Apple Bottom, I don't mean to sound like
a [__] but
>> but you're going to be [__]
>> I thought you and Care Package were
doing at least a bit better off than
this.
>> Care package hasn't been able to do his
mail deliveries because he's been in the
psych ward. We're not made of money like
you and Saurin. All we've got between us
is my fat butt and his obsessive love
for me because I'm such a catch. But we
obviously can't monetize that.
>> Why don't you ask your parents for
money?
>> You know how my mommy and daddy are?
They don't care about me. And we kicked
care packages dad out and he moved two
floors above us because we don't need
him knowing how mentally messed up his
sexy son is.
Drink your macaroni water before it gets
cold, [__]
The pot. Look at the pot. sprinkles. But
where's your portion?
>> I'm not hungry. I'm giving you all the
noodles because I love you like that.
>> Why did you put sprinkles in the pot?
>> You just saw his eyes wander because
he's autistic and the sprinkles are a
good way to remind him there's food in
front of him.
>> We should play a game.
>> How about a good old game from my own
country? Russian roulette.
>> Wow, I didn't know you were crazy. Like
that clean sweep.
>> What's Russian roulette? We take a
revolver and put one bullet inside. Then
we hold it up to our heads and pulls the
trigger. If it does not go off, we hand
it to another pony until it goes all the
way around the table. Clean sweep.
There's six of us. What does that mean?
>> I shouldn't have to tell you that
mathematically if there are five blanks
and one live round, at least one of us
will be shot.
>> That is not even how eat folks. WATCH
THIS.
>> OH MY GOD. OH MY GOD.
OH MY GOD.
>> Greetings one and all. The sex bomb of
the pie family, Octavia Pie, has
arrived.
>> It's you. You're the one in charge of
destroying our farm.
>> This is true. Octavia came looking to
get the signatures from Big Mac and
Clean Sweep as they are part of the
current residence of the Apple family
farm. It's a formal contract stating
that you approve of the Wonderbolts and
Ponyville's joint demolition project.
But I'll have you know now that this is
all just for formality. The wrecking
balls and bulldozers are beating setup
as we speak and are SET TO DESTROY ALL
IN ITS PATH TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
GOODNESS, what is that horrid noise that
disrupts Octavia?
>> It's the fire alarm. It takes AAA
batteries and we don't got any. Well,
Octavia Pi supposes Octavia should do at
least one good deed before Octavia
destroys every single life among the
Earth pony masses. Octavia carries
around AAA batteries in his ass because
Octavia is gay.
>> Care package. Why did you do that? We
needed new batteries.
>> The head of the demolition project is
dead. That puts the project on hold for
a little bit.
>> Earth ponies have already been losing
rights by the day. If the demolition
master goes missing, all eyes are going
to be on the Earth ponies now,
especially the ones in this room. And
I'm too sexy to be charged for murder.
I'm not going to be a part of this.
Yeah, Big Mackie is too sexy to be
charged for murder.
>> When Care Package starts acting this
way, I just let things run its course.
You know how it is.
>> Bottom, don't talk to them.
An arm is still moving. That's just a
postmortem spasm.
>> Hitting it like that doesn't do
anything. It's already dead.
Both of you duck. I don't want you
looking out the window
>> care package. It's the popo.
>> Do you ponies know why I stopped you
tonight?
>> What could possibly be the reason?
Officer
>> Twilight Sparkle, Celestia's famed
apprentice. Saurin, my eternal rival who
stole my faded spot as Ollyorn that I
will someday get my revenge for.
>> What are you doing playing cop?
>> With Earth ponies about to be displaced,
Celestia needed all hands on deck to
keep the pony masses under her strict
control. I see there are two Earth
ponies here, members of the Apple family
at that in a car headed directly into
the woods in the middle of the night. A
strange coincidence as the Apple family
farm is set to be the demolition site
for the Wonderbolts new racetrack.
I think we should beat their asses.
Twilight, if we turned off our body
cams, no pony would ever know.
>> Pinkie Pie, control your blood lust. As
an Earth pony, you're going to soon lose
your pony rights. So, it's best to learn
to stay quiet now. We're just going
camping. Cousin Applejack knows all
about it. It's something we've been
planning for weeks.
>> Applejack is refusing to talk to me
because she's acting like a jealous baby
over my everrowing unicorn rights. So, I
can't exactly verify that, which is
mighty convenient for the lot of you.
So, I have no choice but to believe you.
I stopped to say you were driving on the
outside lane instead of the inside lane
like you're supposed to. But I suppose
now that that's settled, I'll send you
on your way with a warning.
>> Happy days.
That could have been bad. I don't have a
license.
>> Can we go back to town now so I can
change my diaper? I'm such a stinky
poopy baby who pooped a whole lot in my
diaper.
>> You're going to have to marinate in your
waist just a bit longer, Pinkie Pie.
Turn the headlights off. We're going to
follow these [__] at a distance.
Something about this whole thing seems
off.
>> Start digging there, there, and there.
Three holes.
>> How peculiar. Saurin, why does Care
Package want us to dig three holes when
there's only one dead body here?
Brayburn, I'm going to ask you this
because I genuinely love you. Are you
[__]
>> Move aside, Apple Bottom. Your hole
should be big enough.
No.
>> Brayburn, are you okay? I'm by the car.
>> Come down from there.
>> No. You want to unal alive me?
>> You have 5 seconds tops to get down
here. Or I'm sticking my special horn
into your cute little cousin here.
>> Special horn? Is that what you call your
knife cuz you're special? You know, like
the [__] kind of special. Brayburn,
stop egging him on.
>> Wait, you're going to stab me? Back off.
>> You want to save Apple Bottom, don't
you?
>> You want to eat my ass?
>> Brayburn, stop it.
>> Saurin,
>> grab my hoof and I can fly us out of
here.
>> But then we'd be leaving Apple Bottom.
>> He knows what he got himself into dating
care package.
>> Fine then, you coward. Apple bottom it
is then.
>> Wait, you're not actually being serious,
are you?
>> No. Wait, apple bottom.
>> Gotcha.
>> Oh, sweet nibts.
We just came out here to bury the body
and save the farm. Why are you acting
like this?
>> When you've got everyone around you
calling you crazy long enough, then you
start to really go crazy.
>> What the hell do you think you're doing?
>> Sorry. I guess I'm flying a bit too high
from the adrenaline.
>> Then let me bring you back down to
Ponyville.
Okay. Okay. You've had your fun. Quit
it. That hurts.
>> These horns aren't supposed to be used
on each other. Remember our rule.
>> I remember now, so pull it out already.
>> It's your turn to pull out. Do it.
>> I said out. What does it look like I'm
doing? Sugar wings.
>> It looks like you're sticking it in
deeper.
>> Why should I care if the family farm is
ran over? They've never done anything
for me. This is just Care Package and
I's idea of a date night. Don't feel
bad. It was going to happen eventually.
>> Stick it in. Sorry. Now, nice and slow.
>> Oh my god, Pinky. Your brother is dead.
I'm so sorry.
>> It's okay. Every pony dies eventually.
>> Damn. First Dolly Parton, then Tim
Curry. Now this this month really sucks
for gay people. We appear to be in a
dangerous position. Pinky. The killers
who took out Dolly Parton and Tim Curry
and your brother may be among us. Why
did you just turn your body cam off?
Girlfriend. Pinky.
You think you're better than us Earth
ponies? Just because you have an
appendage sticking out of your forehead,
[__] you'll all get what's coming to
you. This is an Earth pony revolution.
So, if nobody is going to claim the
body, can I have it?
>> So, I
>> You're under arrest. Earth pony scum.
>> Brayburn and Saurin attacked us. They're
angry about the demolition and even took
out the head of a demolition project.
These Earth ponies have all gone crazy.
>> Sorry about your boy Toy Saurin, but
rules are rules. You're going to have to
pick him up at the psych ward after he's
checked in
>> and care package.
>> What about him? He's a Pegasus like us,
which means he's above the law.
>> Hey, Saurin, you probably already
guessed, but we don't exactly got the
money to bail Brayburn out.
>> But we know you got the funds.
>> Why did you do it?
>> For fun.
>> It's a Saturday night and we didn't have
anything else to do. So, your idea of a
date night is trying to unalive me and
Brayburn for fun. I hope you two know
that I won't be bailing you out anymore.
>> Now, don't be saying something like
that.
>> Hey, Saurin, why are you dressed as
broccoli?
>> Broccoli is Braburn's second favorite
vegetable. I wanted to wear it while I
bail him out this afternoon to make him
happy.
>> Why not dress up as his first favorite
vegetable? His favorite vegetable are
jalapenos, but there weren't any
jalapeno costumes at Party City.
>> Okay, well, me and the Wonderbolts need
to head back to Cloudsdale for some
urgent crap. But at least one of us has
to stay behind to watch over the
demolition process of the Apple family
farm. As second in command, I'm putting
you in charge. You've got a panel before
the committee at 300 p.m., so don't miss
it.
>> The demolition project has been
cancelled for the foreseeable future.
Furthermore, the red lining all across
Ponyville will start to be looked into.
I request all of Ponyville's redlinining
documents to be handed over to me within
1 hour after this panel is finished.
>> This [__] can't do that. Some pony
shoot him with a gun or something.
>> Celestia, you signed the land held by
all Earth ponies within 67 miles over to
the Wonderbolts when the demolition
project began.
>> No, I signed it over to my racist homeg
girl, Spitfire,
>> and Spitfire passed leadership over to
me. Well, then if the demolition project
isn't going through, I want the Earth
Pony's land back.
>> The contract you had us sign
specifically says the following. I hate
Earth Ponies. They are ugly and
inferior. You can have their land. I
don't give a [__] I, Celestia, does not
ever want it back.
>> Is a bad [__] not allowed to be racist?
>> Your own hatred for their kind will come
back to haunt you. I can promise you,
>> Mr. Saurin. Many ponies are afraid to
talk back to Celestia. Where did you get
the massive balls to do so?
>> Well, not many ponies are the olicorn of
time and space like me. If she tries
anything, I'd be able to overpower her.
>> Saurin, do you think the rest of the
Wonderbolts will agree with your
decision today?
>> Can't say for sure they will, but more
than my teammates, they're my friends.
Celestia's hatred for Earth ponies got
my boyfriend sent to the psych ward
today, and that's unforgivable. My
friends, the Wonderbolts will know where
I'm coming from.
>> If you could say anything to the Earth
ponies of Ponyville, what would it be?
>> I'm not even an Earth pony myself. I was
a Pegasus and then I became an alicorn.
I'll never know how hard they've got it
myself. But I know how hard Brabburn had
it. I know how hard his families had it.
How the weight of scornful eyes is a
burden that follows them wherever they
go. I can say right now that we need to
treat Earth ponies as equals. And some
may do that. But absolute change can't
happen overnight. We need to deconstruct
the rules and regulations that would
made to keep them down. Something that I
know I will be able to do with time.
That's why today I'm challenging
Princess Celestia for the role of
Supreme Monarch of Equestria. Attention.
The red lining papers I've been handed
came with historial papers that Celestia
had kept hidden from the public. The
Constitution of Equestria specifically
state that every 100 years the ponies
have a right to vote and choose their
leaders. And yet an election has not
been held on this planet in over 10,000
years. I reveal to you all that Celestia
sits on a throne of lies up in this
[__]
>> What are you trying to say, broccoli
man?
>> We're reopening the elections and we are
going to elect a new monarch in
Celestia's place. I'm announcing here
and now that I will be running as her
opponent for all Earth ponies everywhere
who don't have a voice. Stand by me.
>> Yeah.
>> This video goes out to Dolly Parton, Tim
Curry, Hayden Panitier, Peter Cullen who
voiced Eeyore and Winnie the Pooh, that
guy who voiced Optimus Prime from
Transformers, and all the other
celebrities that have died this month
for some reason. But more importantly,
go support Tamers 1 2 3 4 5 over on
Patreon cuz God knows every one of
Tamer's videos over the past 3 months
have been demonetized.
Tamers is literally living off of cans
of beans.